# **Anubhav Sharma**

Greater Toronto Area, Canada



anubhavsharma960@gmail.com



+1(647)-835-5219



linkedin.com/in/anubhav-sharma-705579b0

## **Summary**

Experienced System Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology, software development and services industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), User Interface/Responsive web design and Web Development. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science and Engineering.

- -- Technical Skills :- HTML and HTML5, CSS,React & Redux, DB, Node.js, JavaScript, MERN Stack, Agile Methodology, GIT,JIRA.
- -- Non-Technical Skills :- Creativity, Attention to detail, Problem- solving skills, Communication skills, Positive attitude.

## **Experience**

### System Engineer

Infosys

Sep 2019 - Aug 2021 (2 years)

Main Project :-

- -Worked on the project as a React Developer mainly focusing on the front-end (UI)
- -Responsible for developing and supporting the website (built on React tech) used to design, customise and add the same to cart for ordering.

### System Engineer Trainee

Infosys

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019 (7 months)

- Trained in Python along with Object-Oriented Programming and DBMS followed by Web Development (mainly focused on .NET).
- Built a generalised Q&A for developers in which a user can add a question, rate, solve anyone's query regarding Softwares and create his/her own blog related to softwares. Technology used was Angular

# Software Development Intern

OneLXP by illumnus®

May 2018 - Jul 2018 (3 months)

- -Worked on Front-End as well as on Back-end of the website.
- Explored many technologies and the versions of Angular. i.e. Angular, Angular 2, Angular 4, Angular 6 (latest)
- Used and worked on various cloud based platforms such as Heroku and Docker.
- For official communication used Slack application.

# UX Designer Intern

#### Quinka

Apr 2018 - Jul 2018 (4 months)

- Learnt paper prototyping and created some of the mobile application pages based on those learning.
- Designed and explored the Logo for the same.

### **Education**



### Humber College

Postgraduate Degree, Web development

Sep 2021 - Aug 2022

- Learning to develop the websites and web services for multiple environments including DB driven programming, content management and mobile services.
- Simultaneously working on websites that meet strict business and development requirements.

Major topics: -Interaction design studio. -Web development and its special topics.



### Jaypee University of Engineering and Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Jul 2015 - Jun 2019

- Undergrad degree mainly focused on solving problems and designing hardware and software
- Involved the design and development of systems based on computers and complex digital logic devices.

#### **Skills**

Web Development • Front-End Development • Back-End Web Development • Responsive Web Design • User Experience Design (UED) • User Interface Design • User Experience (UX) • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Agile Methodologies • JavaScript